mystockstream.com 2016-01-04

# MyStockStream

Stockstream Financial Advisory Services LLP (henceforth referred to as Stockstream LLP) and mystockstream.com is committed to protecting your personal information and privacy. The clauses listed in this statement apply to all current, former, registered or unregistered users of the website. The clauses listed in this section are subject to changes from time to time without notice. It is the responsibility of the user to regularly visit this section to review the updated Privacy Policy.

#### Personal Information

Mystockstream.com may collect personal information from users like name, email id, profession, profile picture, date of birth, etc for business and verification purposes and to provide customized services to the users. This information in part or whole may be displayed on the profiles of the users. By registering on the website the users confirm that the information they have provided in accurate and their own personal information.

Post registration we may monitor user activities on the website including communications with other users to determine any breach of the Terms of Use and compliance with other local laws and regulations.

User information collected by mystockstream.com may be transferred and stored in a country which may be different from the country of your residence. This may include countries which may have inadequate privacy laws. Information collected by mystockstream.com will under any circumstances be governed by the Privacy Policy as described in this section. 

#### Use of Cookies

Cookies are small files stored on your computer that may be used by websites for tracking purposes.Mystockstream.com may access cookies on your computer to monitor your activities on the website and gain more information about Internet traffic routing to the website. This will strictly be to ensure compliance, improve our services or for other business needs.

#### Confidentiality

Any information provided by users on the website or collected by montoring user activities, through cookies or by other means will be kept confidential as far as possible. Access to user personal information will be limited to individuals and third parties identified in this document and to the employees of the company. Employees of the company (permanent or contract) having access to user information will be required to sign a non disclosure agreement.

#### Sharing Information

Personal information collected from users may be shared with affiliates of mystockstream.com for business purposes such as but not limited to maintaining customer accounts, ensuring compliance or informing customers about new products and services. Affiliates having access to user information will maintain privacy to user information in accordance with the clauses identified in this statement.

Mystockstream.com may also share user personal information with third party vendors providing support services in areas including but not limited to account maintenance, IT, legal, accounting or other professional services.

Mystockstream.com may also disclose user personal information with third parties to insure compliance with local laws and regulations.Such situations will include but may not be limited to subpoenas, warrants or any acts to preserve the personal safety of members or in the general public interest. We may also keep, use and share user information after termination of their accounts if required for legal compliance or fraud detection purposes. 

#### Limitation of Liability

Stockstream LLP and Mystockstream.com will not be financially or otherwise liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, punitive or otherwise loss, injury or damage due to use or release of Personal User Information including but not limited to any loss of business, revenue, data or otherwise. 

Stockstream LLP and Mystockstream.com will take all necessary efforts to keep user data secure and confidential in accordance with the Privacy Policy described in this section. We will not be financially or otherwise liable to any loss of business, revenue, data or otherwise due to loss of Personal User Information by hacking into or stealth from the company servers. 

#### Disclaimers

Please review the Risk Disclaimer for the website. All users of the website (registered or unregistered) acknowledge that they understand the disclaimers listed in the Risk Disclaimer for the website.

#### Limitation of Liability

Please review the Limitation of Liability clauses in the Terns of Use, Risk Disclaimer and Privacy Policy for the website. All users of the website (registered or unregistered) acknowledge that they understand and acknowledge the Limitation of Liability for Stockstream LLP and mystockstream.com.

#### Governing Laws

The clauses listed in the Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and Risk Disclaimer, including any future variations or modifications, will be governed in accordance with the laws of India. By using the website either as a registered or unregistered user you agree to submit to the courts of India for the settlement of any disputes concerning the Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and Risk Disclaimer or their enforcement.
